Joshua Gbogodor

An innovative Software Engineer with years of experience managing all aspects of Software Testing Life Cycle, designing and developing software for business solutions using the latest and most appropriate technology.

7 Asajon Way,Sangotedo Ajah, Lagos State, Nigeria, NG. +2347062164266 joshuagbogodor@gmail.com https://github.com/Lilzj https://www.linkedin.com/in/joshu agbogodor/

EXPERIENCE

Decagon, Lagos — Software Engineer

MARCH 2021- PRESENT

- Built projects with C#, Asp.net, Asp.net core MVC, and Javascript.
- Handled Database Management System with SQL Server, MySQL and SQLite.
- Experience writing unit and integration test.
- A member of a team that developed a Livestock web Application

APTECH, Ibadan — Faculty

JUNE 2020 - February 2021

As a faculty in APTECH, I,

- Taught HTML, CSS, Javascript, Bootstrap, PHP, Angular
- Managed database using SQL Server

PROJECTS

Portfolio Management System

Using the ASP.NET MVC, this project was a simple portfolio to showcase my details and professional qualifications as well as my educational background.

Technologies Used - C#, .Net Core MVC, SQLite, Docker, Heroku.

Link: https://joshdev.herokuapp.com/

JBank Application:

A Banking Application that models a real bank application. Users can sign up and perform all transactions supported by the account.

Technologies Used: .NET Core, Window Form, Microsoft SQL Server and EF Core.

Link: https://www.github.com/Lilzi/IBank

TECHNOLOGY

- C#
- ASP.NET CORE.
- Entity Framework Core
- MVC Architecture
- ADO.NET
- Entity Relational
- HTML 5
- CSS 3
- JavaScript
- Angular
- PHP
- Laravel
- React
- React Hooks
- RESTful API
- MySQL
- SQLite
- SQL server
- Swagger
- Postman
- Jira
- Version Control with Git and GitHub
- Test-Driven Development
- Heroku
- Docker

EDUCATION

University of Nigeria - Bsc

NOVEMBER 2014 - AUGUST 2018

Bachelor of Science degree in Computer Science From University Of Nigeria, Nigeria.